Santo Sinar Pandean

Cybersquare Apex Tower Cyberjaya, Selangor santo.pandean@gmail.com



Summary

I'm 22 Years Old, i have been working in 3 types of companies until now. The first one is Integrated Web Company, the second one is Financial Technology Company, and the last one Blockhain solution / consultant company. I have been built some e-commerce website, Initial Coin Offering (ICO) system, and storage private blockchain. I have worked around with Solidity (Ethereum Virtual Machine), php (laravel), SQL (mySql, oracle), noSql(mongoDB), nodeJs, and vueJs.

Education

Xaverius 1 Pahoman Bandarlampung - Indonesia

High School Graduated July 2013

Multimedia Nusantara University - Indonesia

Degree (Computer Science) Graduated February 2017

I'm taking computer science for my degree. I graduated with $GPA: 3.8\ (max: 4.00)\$ and TOEIC: 800.

Employment History

Cv. Nukegraphic Indonesia

Web Developer (Part Time) June 2016 – May 2017

I built core engine for Sales Portal Company, HRIS Application, and E-commerce Website (http://mama-tina.com/)

Bitcoin.co.id Crypto Exchange (Indodax) - Indonesia

Web & Blockchain Dev

September 2017 – May 2018

In <u>bitcoin.co</u>.id i have been built Analytic's Application (Internal), Prototype platform for ICO Incubator, website and payment gateway system for Tokenomy ICO (Managed to raise funds of approximately 15 million dollars).

Blockchain Technology Malaysia (BTM) - Malaysia

Fullstack & Blockchain Developer

May 2018 - Present

In BTM, I have been built Private Storage Blockchain using IPFS and Multichain as DHT. I also have been built internal Voting DApp for BTM. Mostly, I use VueJs as frontend, electron and nodeJs as backend.

Public Speaking Experience

Topic: Fundamental Of Blockchain - How actually Bitcoin works

Conference

Time: 19 July 2018

Place: Arjuna Street Number 28, Tj Duren, Jakarta (Ralali's Office)

Topic : Security Vs Utility Token

Crypto and Blockchain Meetup

Time: 5 October 2018

Place: Malaysia Global Innovation and Creative Centre, Persiaran Apec, Cyberjaya, Malaysia

Certification

Certified Solidity Developer (CSD) – Ethereum Smart Contract Developer from **Blockchain**

Council

https://www.credential.net/6nv6jpyb

Hobbies & Interests

Swimming, playing badminton, watching movie, and doing some research about new technology.

Professional Skills

Solidity: Advanced Php: Advanced SQL: Advanced NodeJs: Advanced VueJs: Advanced Golang: Beginner Jquery: Advanced Linux: Advanced

Blockchain: Intermediate

IPFS : Advanced Multichain : Advanced

Languages

Indonesia: Native

English: Conversational

Public Repository

https://github.com/santosinarp